<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <provider>
    <System>Game Boy Advance</System>
    <software>Skraper</software>
    <database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
    <web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
  </provider>
  <game id="84406" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).gba</path>
    <name>Pokémon Emerald Version</name>
    <desc>The Hoenn region is unstable--Rayquaza has awakened! Your skills as a Trainer will be challenged like they've never been challenged before as you try to maintain the balance between Kyogre &amp; Groudon. Prove your skills by earning badges &amp; gaining access to the Battle Frontier--the front line of Pokémon battling that offers a whole new level of competition. Never-before-experienced battles await you! 
 
-The third adventure with new episodes in the Hoenn region! 
-Tons of new features, including surprising plot twists and changes to where and how often you can catch certain Pokémon! 
-Use the Game Boy Advance Wireless Adapter to trade &amp; battle between Pokémon Emerald and Pokémon FireRed &amp; LeafGreen versions. 
-Expand your collection when you trade with a friend. Using a Game Link cable, link up with Pokémon Ruby &amp; Sapphire, Pokémon FireRed &amp; LeafGreen or Pokémon Colosseum to catch them all! See instruction booklet for details.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>20050501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Freak</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
    <players>1-5</players>
    <hash>1F1C08FB</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="84408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pokemon - FireRed Version (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).gba</path>
    <name>Pokémon FireRed Version</name>
    <desc>In this adventure, you travel through the Kanto region, form a close bond with your Pokémon, and catch various species to complete the Pokédex. Challenge other trainers, stand up to Team Rocket, and battle the Gym Leaders to earn all eight badges. With these in your possession, you can take on the Elite Four and ultimately face the reigning Champion in a final, decisive battle. Your goal: Become the best trainer and catch them all!</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>20040909T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Freak</developer>
    <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
    <genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <hash>84EE4776</hash>
    <image>./media/images/Pokemon - FireRed Version (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Pokemon - FireRed Version (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).png</thumbnail>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>